vt.edu 2015-06-23

# Privacy Statement | Virginia Tech | Virginia Tech

Virginia Tech has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web page: www.vt.edu.

## Information Automatically Logged

The server collects the IP address, date, time, page accessed, browser type, and the referring page if present. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web page. The date and time are used to track the load on the server and peak usage times. We record the browser type to monitor market penetration of various web browsers so we can better determine what Internet technologies we may utilize in the design of our pages. We use page referrer data--that is, information about the web page that pointed you to our page--to determine to what extent our page is referenced by other resources on the web. These data may be used to preserve the integrity of our computing resources.

### Logging of Quicklink Usage

The Virginia Tech website logs all usage of the quicklinks to assist us in determining the popularity of links. No personally identifiable information is recorded; only the time and date, and the quicklink used.

## Use of Cookies

The Virginia Tech home page issues and reads cookies to track any customization options you may have selected. These include modifications to the list of Quicklinks, the campus image on the page, and whether drop-down menus are activated.

## Personal Information

This Web page does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

## Links to Virginia Tech Pages

This site contains links to other Virginia Tech pages. The privacy practices of other pages may vary with the purposes of the page. Consult the privacy statement on each page.

## External Links

This site contains links to other sites. Virginia Tech is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Log file access is restricted to system administrators while stored on the server. Log files are rotated regularly and archived in a secure location. User and password information, if requested, is encrypted before it is transmitted across the network.

Users should also consult [Virginia Tech's policy on Acceptable Use](http://www.policies.vt.edu/7000.pdf). (PDF) Virginia Tech complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect to access to information.

## Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [webmaster@vt.edu](mailto:webmaster@vt.edu).
